

LILIANA PLATON

UI/UX designer & Front-end developer

During my experience as an Office Administrative and CAD Technical Draftsman, I gained valuable experience in both administrative tasks and technical skills, as well as adaptability, a designoriented mindset, social skills, and organizational abilities. These skills allow me to work efficiently in a team environment and maintain a keen focus on detail. Currently, I am focusing on web development. To gain experience and knowledge in this area, I have completed courses, built a portfolio, and I keep learning from resources like Udemy, CS50, Stack Overflow, freeCodeCamp, MDN and Daily.dev.

CONTACT

- (+40) 757 536 817
- Cluj-Napoca, Romania
- github.com/lilianaplaton
- in linkedin.com/in/lilianaplaton/
- → platonliliana1409@gmail.com
- portfoliolilianaplaton.netlify.app

PORTFOLIO



SKILLS

Figma | Photoshop | HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | UI/UX design Learning React | Bootstrap | MS Office | Brand & Identity | GIT

Problem-solving. Research. Teamwork. Self-study. Communication. Curiosity. Creativity. Result-oriented and pragmatic. Empathy

WORK EXPERIENCE

Office Administrative

Ian 2020 - Feb 2023 | General Proex S.R.L., Cluj-Napoca

- Maintaining financial accountability, managing accounts;
- Brand & Identity (creating template designs for Gmail signature, agenda, documents, technical memory projects, bags, tags, and badges);
- Preparing and redacting documents and technical memory projects;
- Manage phone calls, emails, and going on meetings/delegations;
- Order and maintain inventory of office supplies and equipment;
- Organizing and maintaining records, files, and databases;
- Operating and maintaining office equipment (printer/scanner/plotter).

CAD Technical Draftsman

2017 - 2019 | Visionarh Dessin S.R.L., Cluj-Napoca

- Drafting drawings based on sketches;
- Rendering of buildings/facades in the 3D Studio Max program;
- Detailing the models (execution drawings);
- Checking graphic documentation;
- Elaboration of drawings and presentation in space;
- Rectification of plan/construction in photoshop.

CERTIFICATIONS

Certificate | DECIDFR • Postgraduate training program, UTCN
Sept 2021 - Feb 2022 | Making websites and applications for www

• It is a course for those who want to learn/create responsive websites using technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, AJAX, and PHP.

Certificate in AutoCAD, Faculty of Machine Building

May 2017 | Technical University of Cluj-Napoca

VOLUNTEER

OSSIMM, Technical University of Cluj-Napoca

2015 - 2016 | Organization of Students from Faculty of Materials and Environmental Engineering

EDUCATION

Technical University of Cluj-Napoca

2017 - 2019 | Master's degree: Faculty of Civil Engineering

• Engineering of Special Technologies in Construction

Technical University of Cluj-Napoca

2013 - 2017 | Bachelor's degree: Faculty of Materials and Environmental Engineering

Engineering and Environmental Protection in Industry

High School "Miron Cristea" Subcetate

2009 - 2013 | Mathematics and Informatics